Oh, pbbt!
(Leonard:)Okay, let's try it this way.
Remember the day we first met...
(Leonard:)...and you asked me to go to your
boyfriend's apartment to get your TV back?
And he was 9 feet tall
and he took my pants off and you said...
What was that? What did you s...?
(Leonard:)Oh, yes. You said you owed me one.
(Penny:)Okay, come on, that's not fair.
(Leonard:)I came home with no pants.
(Penny:)Fine. I'll go over there tomorrow.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)I should probably give you
a heads up about his mother.
(Penny:)What about her?
(Leonard:)She's a delightful woman.
You'll love her.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard,
there's a blond girl, Patsy, here to see you.
(Howard:)Who?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Okay, now she's saying it's Penny.
I don't wanna talk to her.
- Hey.
- Ma.